export const mockCollectedData = [
    {
        participant:"DqEwElGfpFGn1Kg",
        context:"Trial 3 Context",
        question:"how focused were you in the past 30 mins?",
        answer:"not at all",
    },
    {
        participant:"PNUACAlOtixK6WJ",
        context:"Trial 3 Decision",
        question:"How often did you turn to social media during class?",
        answer:"some of the time",
    },
    {
        participant:"DqEwElGfpFn1Kg",
        context:"Trial 3 Context",
        question:"how focused were you in the past 30 mins?",
        answer:"not at all",
    },
    {
        participant:"pyXohwL8MTzWbZE",
        context:"Trial 3 Decision",
        question:"How hard it was to stay focused on your homework?",
        answer:"all of the time",
    },
    {
        participant:"vpmInU062coMv3v",
        context:"Trial 3 Context",
        question:"how focused were you in the past 30 mins?",
        answer:"not at all",
    },
    {
        participant:"PNUACAlOtixK6WJ",
        context:"Trial 3 Decision",
        question:"How often did you turn to social media during class?",
        answer:"some of the time",
    },
    {
        participant:"tIIpo2MR8v4fxxV",
        context:"Trial 3 Context",
        question:"how focused were you in the past 30 mins?",
        answer:"not at all",
    },
    {
        participant:"pyXohwL8MTzWbZE",
        context:"Trial 3 Decision",
        question:"How hard it was to stay focused on your homework?",
        answer:"all of the time",
    },
    {
        participant:"vpmInU062coMv3v",
        context:"Trial 3 Context",
        question:"how focused were you in the past 30 mins?",
        answer:"not at all",
    },
    {
        participant:"PNUACAlOtixK6WJ",
        context:"Trial 3 Decision",
        question:"How often did you turn to social media during class?",
        answer:"some of the time",
    },
    {
        participant:"tIIpo2MR8v4fxxV",
        context:"Trial 3 Context",
        question:"how focused were you in the past 30 mins?",
        answer:"not at all",
    },
    {
        participant:"pyXohwL8MTzWbZE",
        context:"Trial 3 Decision",
        question:"How hard it was to stay focused on your homework?",
        answer:"all of the time",
    },
    {
        participant:"tIIpo2MR8v4fxxV",
        context:"Trial Tester Questions",
        question:"how focused were you in the past 30 mins?",
        answer:"not at all",
    },
    {
        participant:"pyXohwL8MTzWbZE",
        context:"Trial Tester Questions",
        question:"How hard it was to stay focused on your homework?",
        answer:"all of the time",
    },
    {
        participant:"tIIpo2MR8v4fxxV",
        context:"Trial Tester Questions",
        question:"how focused were you in the past 30 mins?",
        answer:"not at all",
    },
    {
        participant:"pyXohwL8MTzWbZE",
        context:"Trial Tester Questions",
        question:"How hard it was to stay focused on your homework?",
        answer:"all of the time",
    }
]